# Masamichi Junior Tsukada

Mississauga, Ontario L5L2z7 647-927-4170 Tsukada.m@hotmail.com

#### SUMMARY

Independent game developer with 3+ years of experience developing indie games, applications, and websites using a variety of programming languages and technologies. Exceptional project management skills, and has a drive and passion to create new and challenging video games for console, mobile and, VR

### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

### Languages

- Proficient in C#, Java, C++, HTML/CSS
- Familiar with JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, C, Lua, Kotlin, Bootstrap

#### Software

- Game Engines: Unity, Godot, Game Maker Studio, Unreal Engine
- · Other: Figma, Justinmind, Audacity, Gimp

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Lead Game Developer / Co-Creator - Kalios

January 2021 - Current

- Worked with two other developers and project managed a complete game development lifecycle to create Kalios using C# and unity scripts.
- Gained valuable experience on how user feedback in the testing stage has a huge impact on the success of the project.
- Designed, developed, and tested Kalios as well as providing other developers with help regarding the project.
- Responsible for programming the character functionality, levels, the procedural generation of levels and the UI system.

# **Programming Instructor**

October 2020 - Current

### Code Ninja's Oakville

- Instructed kids and young teens in computer science principles and concepts, and programming languages.
- worked with other programming instructors to devise and implement support plans to help younger kids learn computer science.

## **UI Designer - Mobile App**

January 2019 - April 2019

• Led the overall design vison, and production of visual designs and wire frames of the mobile app.

### **EDUCATION**

### Sheridan College

September 2018-Current

Oakville, Ontario

Advanced diploma in software development and network engineering